{
    "subject": "Cliff_Robertson",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "J._W._Coop",
    "human_readable": "Cliff Robertson created J.W. Coop.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8204297423362732,
            "question": "Who created the character J.W. Coop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8068714141845703,
            "question": "Is Cliff Robertson known for creating characters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6279404759407043,
            "question": "What role did Cliff Robertson play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6213598847389221,
            "question": "What is Cliff Robertson famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48954784870147705,
            "question": "What is the name of the character played by Cliff Robertson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47204622626304626,
            "question": "Who was responsible for bringing J.W. Coop to life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46081843972206116,
            "question": "What kind of character is J.W. Coop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45656463503837585,
            "question": "Besides acting, what else is Cliff Robertson known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42021292448043823,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the character J.W. Coop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38670799136161804,
            "question": "Is there a movie or show featuring J.W. Coop?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Cliff Robertson created J.W. Coop.",
            "html": "yago_22828_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the character J.W. Coop?",
            "html": "yago_22828_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides acting, what else is Cliff Robertson known for?",
            "html": "yago_22828_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of character is J.W. Coop?",
            "html": "yago_22828_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22828_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22828_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22828_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22828_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22828_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22828_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22828_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22828_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22828_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22828_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Cliff Robertson was involved in the creation of \"J. W. Coop\" as both a director and a writer, aligning with the statement that he created it."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}